[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The slogan of this Japanese car make, founded on September 24, 1948, is The Power of Dreams.", "correct_answer": "Honda", "incorrect_answers": ["Nissan", "Suzuki", "Yamaha"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which three left-handed US Presidents served in succession?", "correct_answer": "Bill Clinton, George H. W. Bush, Ronald Reagan", "incorrect_answers": ["Herbert Hoover, Franklin Delano Roosevelt, Harry Truman", "George H. W. Bush, Bill Clinton, George W. Bush", "James Garfield, Herbert Hoover, Gerald Ford"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the condition, from which the main character suffers in Memento?", "correct_answer": "Anterograde Amnesia", "incorrect_answers": ["Multiple sclerosis", "Schitzophrenia", "Constipation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these ski resorts is not located in the Alps?", "correct_answer": "Mont-Tremblant", "incorrect_answers": ["Kitzbuhel", "Zermatt", "Chamonix-Mont-Blanc"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress, famous for playing in the series The Avengers, portrays Tracy Draco, in On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "Diana Rigg", "incorrect_answers": ["Claudia Cardinale", "Vanessa Redgrave", "Senta Berger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of Ghana before the country gained its independence?", "correct_answer": "The Gold Coast", "incorrect_answers": ["The Belgian Congo", "Ivory Coast", "Limpopo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "U.S. President Hardings administration was rocked by this scandal, involving oil.", "correct_answer": "Teapot Dome", "incorrect_answers": ["Livingston-Heathcote", "Skull Island", "Credit Mobilier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Coca-Cola was originally green.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was Aristotles most famous student?", "correct_answer": "Alexander", "incorrect_answers": ["Phillippus Magnus", "Erasmus", "Ptolemy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Its the middle of July. You are in Louisville, KY, USA and you cross over the Ohio River into Jeffersonville, IN. You have effectively gone:", "correct_answer": "Backwards in Time", "incorrect_answers": ["Forward in Time", "Time Stands Still", "You have broken the time continuum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What company is the manufacturer of Mr. Goodbar?", "correct_answer": "Hershey", "incorrect_answers": ["Mars", "Nestle", "none of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Eddie Murphy plays a street hustler in the movie Trading Places.  What was his name in the movie?", "correct_answer": "Billy Ray Valentine", "incorrect_answers": ["Moses Gunn", "Malcolm Campbell", "Herschel Walker"]}]